By the time you'd reached
me, it was too late.
Death has me now.
What the...
Up above them, it's a helicopter!
Either way, those morons
have no means of escape.
Admittedly, the weather is quite lovely
for a blind date at the Coliseum.
It's a shame that Green Tea
and I will have to rain on it.
We have to exterminate the mold before
it has a chance to reach the Coliseum.
Bucciarati, our underground friend.
I'm leaving him to you.
Go on ahead.
I'll take care of this one.
Right.
Let's get out of here.
It's all the same.
My first victim will be you, Bucciarati.
I'm coming to the moon
and I'll be back in time.
I'm coming back to the moon
I'll be back in time.
Let's
go.
The end of the year is
the end of the year.
We will be able to
survive the past.
The end of the year is
the end of the year.
The end
of the year
is the end of the year.
I'm going to go to the world.
I'm going to die!
When I die, I'm going to die.
I'm going to die?
Hell no!
I'm going to die
Yeah, ambushed me like that earlier.
I really hope for your sake
that you've learned a new trick
Cuz I'm not falling for it
this time you dirty son of a!
Son
Dirty son of a flood.
No
You dirty son of a brick, son
of a porch and awaited the word!
You want his bitch?
I knew that, what you some
kind of language experts?
Damn bastard-o!
I almost forgot I'm supposed
to get this on tape.
Killing you shouldn't
take more than a second.
Let's see...
Zippermen!
How...
how did he react so fast?
If this fight's gonna be a one-on-one,
then there won't be a need
for me to go underground.
Nearly got me there.
His powers eclipse Zippermans,
both in strength and speed.
Wait, I see.
So that's where his strength comes from.
It's the elbow strikes to the ground.
He's using the recoil
to augment his punches.
At speed,
it's almost like a boxer trying to spring
off the ropes to get some added snap.
I ain't got all day.
Like I thought there's not
a trace of mold on you?
even though you fell.
I thought Chocolata's green tea was supposed
to ravage any living thing it touches.
So how the hell are
you still in one piece?
Guess I'll just have to do
it the old-fashioned way!,
beating you over and over again.
until your body stops moving.
Welcome to my sanctuary!
Giorno Giovanna.
The new thorn in my side.
Damn bread is able to breathe
life into inanimate objects,
just like he did with
those straight bullets.
The plans gripping this helicopter
couldn't have come from any other source.
You think you're clever, huh?
Well, think again.
Because your pathetic life-granting
powers are impotent before my green tea.
Watch us rot every one of your vines.
We're gonna take off whether they like
it or not, so rain down those spores.
It's time for us to whack a few weeds.
W-what the hell?
This damn thing won't budge at all!
Don't tell me we're really stuck here!
Ah, piece of junk! Good.
It's nearly reached full maturity,
and its grip is coming in strong.
That helicopter isn't gonna
fly off anywhere soon.
Mista, we just have to
climb up to the cockpit.
Great, let's climb a tree, then again.
I could just shoot him from here now
that he's within range of my bullets!
Now, go make Daddy proud.
Our point of impact is that
Katsune skull! What? What?
White?
Mista!
The guys are saying the Stranzo's
nowhere near the helicopter!
What the frickin' hell?
Did he just run off?
There's nowhere to hide in here!
And he couldn't have gone outside!
Guys, get your feelers out!
Hunt his ass down fast!
Number two!
Number three!
Shit, Mista, you gotta call us back quickly
before something else terrible happens!
Mista, what the?
Oh, shit!
Hey, fellas, what the
hell happened to you two?
It can't be.
Why couldn't any of us find him?
Stands are limited to one
per person, I thought.
This guy can attack you
with some killer mold
that eats your body
when you lose altitude,
but that's it!
He shouldn't be able to do anything else!
Run, number one.
Number six, number seven!
We can't defeat him.
So go!
Hurry up!
Get on out of here as fast as you can!
This guy's scary deadly!
Mista, you have to get your
bullets out of there now!
Withdraw your stand right away!
No can't do.
This bastard's got his
claws in there deep.
I can't withdraw jack shit right now.
It looks like my judgment was way off.
Mista, no!
Hey, come on!
Just send me in there and I'll fix this!
I'll bring everyone back
without a problem, I swear!
Don't bother.
That's not a promise you can keep.
There's a good reason why he's holding
on to the bullets he's destroyed.
He knows Mista won't be able to heal
as long as his stand is activated.
There's nothing I can do.
No!
Not to mention,
he's counting on you to
rush in there to save the
day because he knows that
you're the only one left?
and if you die, so does Mista.
I should have known.
This isn't a guy you can
just shoot down from afar.
Mista, I'm leaving Trish and Naracha here.
Yeah.
Watch over them!
Mista! Mista! Number five.
I need you to follow him.
You watched your nose back.
Take this bullet with you.
I'm picking up life energy.
So I don't get why the bullets
couldn't get a lock on him.
I can't nail down his exact spot, but I
know for sure he hasn't left the chopper.
In which case...
Strike him down, Golden Wind!
There's still nothing inside.
What the hell is this guy up to?
This makes zero sense.
There's no way he could hide in there.
Medical supplies?
Is he some kind of doctor?
The chaos is spreading.
Pretty soon, it'll engulf the Colosseum.
We're out of time.
I have to finish this right now,
or we're all going to be screwed.
The real enemy is...
Quick, Number One, come to me!
No, get away from it, Giorno!
You're walking right into a trap!
What the...
What happened?
Is that...
Journal, be careful!
Journal!
Curiosity...
That is the primary fuel in the
engine of intellectual development.
You know,
I never thought I'd be
quite this grateful for all
those human experiments I
conducted during my youth.
So many hours I spent analyzing
and recording which segments
of the human body could be
removed without inducing death.
It shouldn't surprise
you that I therefore know
exactly which veins I must
seal to stop emerging.
Lucky me.
Green tea's mold can perform
this critical sealing,
allowing me to maintain
my freedom of movement?
and the ability to hide wherever
I please even while I'm dissected.
You can't afford to fall
any further, Giorno!
That horrible moat's gonna get
you if you sink lower than that!
Giorno!
You gotta climb for your life!
We all sometimes have those moments
of pure and perfect ecstasy, don't we,
Giorno Giovanna?
There are two scenarios I can think
of where such joy shines on us.
The first one starts with despair.
When a desolate situation becomes
hopeful, one starts to feel blessed.
The very moment your oversized
weeds snatch me out of the sky,
I'll admit I felt something
close to true fear.
And boy, oh boy, was it
a dreadful sensation.
But I cut through the pain.
My years of experience
combined with my sheer
inner fortitude helped me turn the tables.
And let me say, the feelings awaiting
me on the other side were blissful.
Oh, what a rush.
The golden wind!
Who said you could get up?
John, no!
Did you really forget that I still had
two legs crawling about to hear you,
stupid dog?
And just what I was about to share with
you, the second source of happiness.
which occurs when beholding
the weak and pathetic!
Bye-bye!
Long before you hit the cold, hard ground,
my green tea's malt will
have already reduced?
your pitiful body to drink!
Jean, I need this!
Now's your chance!
Hurry up!
Run back inside the chopper!
Crazy!
I owe you one!
Beat the Papa out of him!
Now you're just getting on my nerves!
I'm not sure how many times I can
teach you this lesson, my dear boy.
But I've got plenty of spores to spare!
Do you want to know a funny thing
about these branches of yours?
They're also living things
that my mole loves to eat,
but I hope they don't start to sag.
Hey, don't you stand there and
you're gonna jump! Quickly!
Oh, baby, I want more, show me more, let
me see that pretty-faced train of all hope.
Ooh, I'm all tingly,
you'd think I'd be used to it by now,
but the sweet sight never gets old.
Just be sure to cheat this way so I can get
a good look before you go ahead and die!
Ahahaha!
Bone, looks like my aim for your
propellers was right on the money.
It was a perfect hit.
I knew your putrid mold would
naturally end up consuming my branches.
But, when a branch separates
from its body, it dies.
All that's left is wood.
And because you destroyed the
branch, it returned to bullet form.
Oh, and before I forget about all
that creepy happiness bullshit?
It might surprise you to hear that seeing
you like this, It brings me no joy at all.
Not a bit, though.
Maybe it's cuz I'm the one who's
been winning this whole time
Jeez talk about close you managed to
stop his mold from spreading further
I don't mean to cut your celebration short,
but if you don't mind, scooch a little.
It's possible I'm overthinking
things a bit here.
However, I get the feeling that Cioccolata
guy's faking, that he's just playing dead.
Hey, dick!
No one's gonna buy that lame act!
I know exactly what it is you're plotting!
What are you saying?
Right now, you're likely thinking
to yourself, maybe, just maybe.
If I could only move
a little bit that way,
then I'd be able to escape through the
trench before that stronzo could get to me.
Then I'll disperse more mold.
That's what you're planning
in that sick head, right?
Full disclosure, I'm pretty badly injured.
My right lung has suffered
a sizable puncture.
My subclavian artery
is completely severed.
I've got four cracked ribs,
not to mention my humerus and
carpals are pretty much shot.
Climbing all the way up there to get to
you would present a challenge, I would say.
How lucky for me, then, that my
stand is none other than Golden Wind.
It has power in spades
and a range of two meters.
That means you fall well within its reach.
It'll only take an instant
for us to crush you.
He's dead, Journal!
You already got him right in the noggin!
Not quite.
If you can behave when I get
up there then I promise to show
you a little mercy and you'll
come out of this with your life.
I'm throwing you a rope.
So what'll it be I'm gonna start
making my way to you think hard.
You're getting nowhere near me look
behind you you bungling sucker.
Uh-oh, whose hand is that
on Mista and the turtle?
You dumbass!
The entire time you were
running your worthless mouth,
you didn't even notice my
right arm sneaking toward?
your little friends in the
shadows once, now, did ya?
Well, Mista's throat will
have to pay the price.
Seems you have to choose.
Either you can pursue me, or
you can heal your precious pal.
Who's winning now, worthless fool?
Time to die!
You were close.
I drew out my speech in
order to buy myself time.
The bullet that tore a hole through
your head still had to mature,
before eventually making its
way back to the initial wound.
The shrapnel that drew it
was lodged in your skull,
and returned to its
original form as a beetle.
One whose growth I happened
to accelerate greatly
with golden wind when I
aimed for the propellers.
I wanted to be certain you
were completely neutralized,
meaning I had to finish you off, whether
or not I could still hear a heartbeat.
But, but you said that
if I just stayed still,
that I, I would still
make it out of this alive.
Oh, give me a break.
If you really thought I was being
serious, then you're the worthless fool.
I don't spare pieces of shit.
What did you just call me?
Silence.
This is nothing!
Journal!
Look who's waking up from his nappy nap!
I hate me, mister!
I missed you!
What the?
How'd that get here?
Did Cioccolata drop it?
Don't tell me!
Was he on the phone this entire time?
I didn't even see it. Damn it.
Who the hell did he call?
Come on, come on, pick up!
Cioccolata!
What's the holdup over there?
He doesn't usually take this long. Hello?
Huh?
What's this flashing thingamadoodle?
Do I press something or...
Oh, yeah, that's right.
It means I got a message
in my stupid inbox.
No frickin' duh.
Now let's see here. Wow, there's two.
And wait, I don't remember him calling me.
Was it when I was chasing
Bucciarati earlier today?
Seko, it's me.
Chocolata's back!
I took care of that little
twerp with the gun, Mista. Yay!
But that newcomer Giorno looks like he's
trying to come up to the helicopter.
The sad fool can climb all he wants.
Victory is already mine.
You finish off that Bucciarati.
Do that and I'll give you
the bestest back scratch.
And don't think I forgot the sugar cubes.
Are you ready, boy?
Here they come.
How many you want?
How about two?
All right, you rascal.
I'll give you five.
Oh, I'm winding up.
You gotta catch him
with your muzzle, okay?
Hey, no hands allowed.
Listen, Seiko.
You and I are unstoppable,
and it is the duty of those who are
strong like us to rule over the weak.
One might say we, the mighty,
were charged by the heavens to
guide the frail and the feeble.
Even if the boss numbers among them, not
only will I destroy those irksome louts?
I will transcend the boss himself.
And you shall be by my side,
because you are strong.
Giorno's here. I must go.
Just one more thing.
I want you to know that you
are very dear to me, Seiko.
Talk to you soon.
That malicious mole should
be far behind by now.
But they dare to tell us
what's bad and what's good.
Stand up, join us!
Come on, just see this light!
We are the power, who's in the future?
Because we are the fighters,
just fighting for a ride.
Thank you.